A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1972-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 31515], 1970-1981, Extent: cu. ft. (boxes). (Box 1-)
  - Subject files, ASAP (Alcohol Safety Action Program), 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Cambodia Campaign, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, CETA, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Commonwealth Date Base, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Community Action Agency Program, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Community Education Services, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Community Services Administration, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Correspondence, Peter Clendenin (Asst. for Evaluation Services, HR), 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Correspondence, Jean L. Harris (Secretariat of Human Resources), 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Correspondence, Robert Masden (Asst. for Governmental Services, HR), 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Correspondence, General, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Definitions Task Force, 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, EPSDT (Early and Periodic Screening, Diagnosis, and Treatment), 1978-1981 (Box 68)
  - Subject files, Governors Manpower Services Council, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Governors Secretaries, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, HJR 49, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, HJR 264, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, Office of, Agencies meeting, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, Office of, Brochures, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, Office of, Retreat, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, Office of, Output, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, Office of, Liaison Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Information and Referrals, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Inmate Job readiness, 1978-1981 (Box 69)
  - Subject files, Intern project, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, Division of Crime and Justice, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, LRE, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, Education, Handicapped children, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, Local Government Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, National Governors Association, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, National Governors Association, Policy positions, 1978-1979 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, Northern Virginia projects, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Subject files, Planning districts, 1978-1981 (Box 70)
  - Private Industry Council, CETA, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Planning budget, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Prescription Team Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Virginia Division for Children's Report to the Sec. of Human Resources on the Prescription Team, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Buchanan County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Dickenson County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Dickenson County, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Essex County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Essex County, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Johnson City-Kingsport-Bristol Metropolitan Area, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, King and Queen County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, King and Queen County, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, King William County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Lancaster County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Lee County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Mathews County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Mathews County, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Middlesex County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Middlesex County, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Northern Neck, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Northumberland County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Richmond County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Russell County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Scott County, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Wise County-City of Norton, Data Summary, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Dept. of State Planning and Community Affairs, Wise County-City of Norton, Projections and Economic Base Analysis, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, General, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers, 1978-1981 (Box 72)
  - Governor, Office of, Government Employment and Training Council (GETC), 1978-1981 (Box 72)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Unemployment Institute Trust Fund Study, 1978-1981 (Box 72)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Private Industry Council, 1978-1981 (Box 72)
  - Governor, Office of, Senior Executive Assistant (Larry E. Murphy), 1978-1981 (Box 73)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Comprehensive Employment and Training Act of 1973 Grants, Balance of State, Report on Audit, 1976-1978 (Box 73)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Comprehensive Employment and Training Act of 1973, Subgrantee Grants, 1976-1978 (Box 73)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission, Information Services, 1978-1981 (Box 73)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Virginia Employment Commission (VEC), Personnel (Review), 1978-1981 (Box 73)
  - Governor Conference on Day Care Needs, 1978-1981 (Box 73)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 73)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Budget Advisory Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 73)
  - Governor, Office of, News Summaries, 1980 September-December (Box 73)
  - Governor, Office of, News Summaries, 1981 January-April (Box 74)
  - Governor, Office of, News Summaries, 1981 April-June (Box 74)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor's Committee on the Education of the Handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 74)
  - Health, Dept. of, Equipment orders, changes, deletions, etc., 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Health, Dept. of, Children and Youth, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Health, Dept. of, Review of Health Study VEC-VMCC, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Health, Dept. of, Licensing and permit applications, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Health, Dept. of, DP Standards and procedures, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Study of Manpower Services in Virginia, Draft report and Technical proposal and cost estimate, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - GMSC-GMPC Study, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - CETA, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - VEC-DCS VM Center, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - VEC, RFP, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - VEC Documentation Project, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - VEC and Dept. of Computer Services, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - VEC Equipment orders, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Development of an approach for the implementation of an effective data and information system, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Health Regulatory Boards, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Virginia Board of Medicine, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Dept. of Welfare, Camp Shon Ta'i, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Dept. of Health, Bureau of Toxic Substances Information, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Dept. of Mental Heatlh, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Misc. correpondence, 1977-1979 (Box 76)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, Misc. correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 76)
  - Subject files, Radiological material, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, Refugee and resettlement, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, Rules and regulations, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, Speech file, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, STEP, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, Title XX, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, United Way, 1978-1981 (Box 77)
  - Subject files, Virginia Treatment Center, Title XX, 1978-1981 (Box 78)
  - Subject files, VOPEC, 1978-1981 (Box 78)
  - Subject files, Winterization program, 1978-1981 (Box 78)
  - Subject files, Southern Institute for H.R., Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 78)
  - Subject files, H.R., Portsmouth, 1978-1981 (Box 78)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Development of Information System, 1978-1981 (Box 79)
  - COVIS (Comm. of Va. Information Sciences), 1978-1981 (Box 79)
  - Chronological files, 1976-1977 (Box 79)
  - Chronological files, 1978 (Box 79)
  - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 80)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Congressional Forum, 1979 October (Box 80)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 81)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Seminars, 1978-1981 (Box 81)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Management Exchange and Clearinghouse, 1978-1981 (Box 81)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Briefing information and minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 81)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Studies and Proposals, 1978-1981 (Box 81)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, Publications, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - Humane and Legal Rights Task Force, "Meeting Legal Requirements with Limited Financial Resources," 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - Staus of Women, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - UI Trust Fund, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - CETA, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - Report of state owned surplus lands, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - Review of Key Features with Physical Plant Programs developed for Lynchburg Training School and Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - State Board of Health, Meetings, 1981 (Box 82)
  - Medicaid, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - Legislation, Visually Handicapped, VEC, and Welfare, 1978-1981 (Box 82)
  - Governor, Office of, News summaries, 1981 June-Sept. (Box 83)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Legislative Session for HR Agencies, 1981 (Box 83)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Budget for HR Agencies, 1979 (Box 83)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resources, General, 1978-1981 (Box 83)
  - General, Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1978-1981 (Box 84)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Memorandum and correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 84)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, General, 1978-1981 (Box 85)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 85)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, Travel, 1978-1981 (Box 85)
  - Human Resources, Secretary of, Grand Jury (Otis L. Brown), 1978-1981 (Box 85)
  - JLARC, Program Evaluation of Virginia Drug Abuse Control, 1978-1981 (Box 86)
  - Human Resources, Secretary (Otis L. Brown), Subject files, 1978-1981 (Box 86)
  - Cabinet, Meetings, 1972 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Meetings, 1973 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Meetings, 1974 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Meetings, 1977 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Mission, Goals, Strategies, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Ombudsman Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Printing Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Communications Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Information Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Information Systems Planning and Corrdination Group, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Mail Delivery Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Cabinet, Cabinet papers, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Consolidated Laboratory Services, Legislation, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Consolidated Laboratory Services, Operational Board, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Consolidated Laboratory Services, Operational Board Meeting Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Consolidated Laboratory Services, Personnel 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Consolidated Laboratory Services, General, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Personnel and Resumes, 1978-1981 (Box 87)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Personnel and Resumes, 1978-1981 (Box 88)
  - Council on Narcotics and Drug Abuse Control Resource Manual, 1973 (Box 88)
  - Virginia Comprehensive Health Planning, 1978-1981 (Box 88)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Consolidated Laboratory Services, Budget, 1978-1981 (Box 88)
  - 3% Expenditure Reduction, 1975 (Box 88)
  - Planning Management and Implementation of a low budget household needs assessment survey, 1978-1981 (Box 88)
  - Senate Bill 517 Projects, 1978-1981 (Box 88)
  - Report on State Practices, Part I State Practices Regarding Certificate-Of-Need Standards, 1978-1979 (Box 89)
  - Program Exhibit, Office on Aging, 1980-1982 (Box 89)
  - Program Exhibit, Va. Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, Woodrow Wilson Rehab Center, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Program Exhibit, Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Program Exhibit, State Board of MHMR, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Program Exhibit, Va. Development Disabilities Planning Council, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Sec. of Administration and Finance, Directives, 1978 (Box 89)
  - Legislative Implementation Reports, 1979 (Box 89)
  - Statewide Health Coordinating Council Selection Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 89)
  - Biennial Budget, 1978-1980 (Box 89)
  - Va. State Health Plan, Volumes I and II, 1978-1983 (Box 89)
  - Study of the Feasibility of combining Va. Council for the Deaf and Va. Committee for the Visually Handicapped into Single State Agency, Volume I and II, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Preliminary Va. State Medical Facility Plan, 1979 (Box 89)
  - Attorney General, Office of, General, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Cabinet, General, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Transportation, 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Commerce and Resources (Rowe), 1978-1981 (Box 89)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Education (J. Wade Gilley), 1978-1981 (Box 90)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Public Safety, 1978-1981 (Box 90)
  - Cabinet, Secretary of Administration and Finance (Charles B. Walker), 1978-1981 (Box 90)
  - Governor, Office of, News Summaries, 1981 Sept.-Oct. (Box 90)
  - Cabinet, Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy (Stuart W. Connock), 1978-1981 (Box 90)
  - Governor, Office of, Sr. Executive Assistant (Jennifer Joy Mason), 1978-1981 (Box 91)
  - Governor, Office of, Special Assistant to Governor (Paul G. Edwards), 1978-1981 (Box 91)
  - Governor, Office of, Governor Dalton, Schedules, 1978-1981 (Box 91)
  - Governor, Office of, Washington Liaison Office (Stan Parris), 1978-1981 (Box 91)
  - Division of Heart and Vascular Diseases Presentation to Ntl. Heart, Lung, and Blood Advisory Council, 1978 (Box 91)
  - Budget Bill (House Document No. 1), 1980 (Box 91)
  - State Health Plan, Draft, 1979 May (Box 91)
  - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Annual report, 1977-1978 (Box 91)
  - Va. Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Public Need, 1979 (Box 91)
  - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, Budget, 1979 (Box 91)
  - Project Head Start Community Action Program Office of Economic Opportunity, National Conference, 1967 October (Box 91)
  - Service Integration for Deinstitutionalization, The SID Report, Volumes 1-8, 1978-1981 (Box 91)
  - How Safe is Safe, The Design of Policy on Drugs and Food Additives, National Academy of Science, 1974 (Box 92)
  - Saccharin: Technical Assessment of Risks and Benefits, 1978 (Box 92)
  - Human Resources, Secretary, Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation (Dr. Woodrow W. Wilkerson), 1978-1981 (Box 92)
  - Institute of Medicine, Membership Committee meeting minutes, 1979 October (Box 92)
  - MASD Performance Evaluation, Exhibits, 1978-1981 (Box 92)
  - State Board of Health, Biographical Summaries, 1978-1981 (Box 92)
  - Virginia 1980 Development Disabilities State Plan, 1978-1981 (Box 92)
  - Fifth Annual NAPCRG Meeting, 1977 March (Box 92)
  - Cooperative Study of Sickle Cell Disease (CSSCD), 1978-1981 (Box 92)
  - TAI, 1978-1981 (Box 92)
  - Southwest Virginia Legislative Tour, 1978 November (Box 92)
  - Biennium Budget Bill, 1978-1980 (Box 92)
  - National Academy of Science, Institute of Medicine, National Health Planning Guidelines, 1979 (Box 93)
  - Saccharin: Technical Assessment of Risks and Benefits, 1978 (Box 93)
  - Proposed System for Food Safety Assessment, 1978 (Box 93)
  - Food Safety Regulation and Societal Impacts, 1978 (Box 93)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Memorandum, 1978 (Box 93)
  - Budget, Emergency Budget Requests, 1981 (Box 93)
  - Budget, Mini session, 1981 (Box 93)
  - Budget, Capital Outlay requests, 1980-1982 (Box 93)
  - Budget, Capital Outlay requests, 1980-1982 (Box 94)
  - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Memorandum, 1978-1981 (Box 94)
  - Personal correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Training Task Force, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Training Task Force, Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Education of the Handicapped, Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Task force to revise state plan for identification and diagnosis of handicapped children, July 25 draft, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Task force to revise state plan for identification and diagnosis of handicapped children, August 19 draft, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Task force to revise state plan for identification and diagnosis of handicapped children, September 2 draft, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Revised Virginia state plan for identification and diagnosis of handicapped children, 1977 September (Box 95)
  - Recommendations by Agencies, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Pennsylvania and Maryland policies for handicapped children, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - 5.11 Education of handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - 94-142 Federa regulations, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Early and Periodic screening, diagnosis, and treatment program for childrens's health, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Migrant grant, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Governor's Committee on Education of Handicapped children, Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Plan for identification and diagnosis, Shanholtz plan, 1972 (Box 95)
  - Merger of Deaf and Blind Departments, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - A-95 information, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - George A. Koger, Correspondence to and from, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Legislative tracking system, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Paul W. Matthias, Correspondence to and from, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Correspondence, General, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Governor's memorandum, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Dept. of Health, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Visually handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Vocational rehabilitation, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Virginia Developmental disabilities, Planning and Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - Virginia Commission for Children and Youth, 1978-1981 (Box 95)
  - A Proposal for Training Services for Virginia, 1977 (Box 96)
  - Dr. Harris, Memorandum to, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Mrs. Hill, Memorandum to, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Agencies meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Memos to Agency heads, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Staff, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Human Resources, Office of, Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Governor, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - State of the State material, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Jennifer Joy Manson, Correspondence to and from, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Governor, Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Administration and Finance, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Marilyn Lussen, Memorandum to, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - General Assembly members, Correspondence to and from, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Letters to Congressional Delegates on Formula Grants funding, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Presentation for Attorney General J. Marshall Coleman, 1981 (Box 96)
  - What is Human Resources?, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Proposals for training Human Resources at VCU and UVA, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Peter C. Clendenin, COrrespondence to and from, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Southern Institute for Human Resource, Conference, 1979 October (Box 96)
  - Manpower Utilization Plan, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Human Resources Planning Retreat II, 1978 December (Box 96)
  - Human Resources Planning Retreat III, 1979 December (Box 96)
  - DCS (Dept. of Computer Services) Plan, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - Data processing, 1978-1981 (Box 96)
  - HB 282, State data processing, 1978 (Box 96)
  - SJR 58, 1978 (Box 97)
  - Systems Development Standards Workbook, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Staff report on Title XX of the 1974 Social Security Act Amendments, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Education of the Handicapped, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Aging, Office of, 3 year plan, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Council for the Deaf, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Interpreter Services, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Ralph Cantrell files (Asst. for Management Services), 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Development Disabilities Planning and Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Development Disabilities Protection and Advocacy, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Virginia, Developmental Disabilities State Plan, 1981 (Box 97)
  - Dept. of Health, Regulatory Boards, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
  - Subject files, A-B, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Applicants, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Board member lists, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Brochures, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, CDC Va. Venture, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Citizen correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Deaf/Blind Study, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, E-F, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Overall Advisory Council on Needs of Handicapped Children and Adults, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, PMIS (Personnel Management Information System), 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, QRS, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Rehab Act, Section 504, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, SIHR HR Conference, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, State Cars, Rules and Regulations, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Traffic violations in state vehicles, Letters, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Technical Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Television program "Where," 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Travel reports, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Subject files, Education of Handicapped Children, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Family Life Commission, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Federal government, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Federal grants, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, GETC (Governors Employment and Training Council), 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, Planning Retreats, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Human Resources, General, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Local Government Advisory Council, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - Subject files, Local Option Task Force, 1978-1981 (Box 99)
  - HJR 294, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Human Resources Agency Studies for Governor and General Assembly, 1981 (Box 100)
  - CSA Block Grant information, 1978-1981 (Box 100)
  - CETA Objectives, 1978-1981 (Box 100)
  - Metropolitan Ambulance vs. State Commisioner of Health, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Budget, 1981 (Box 100)